# **Teresa Struzek**

## **Graphic Designer/Web Designer**

Mesa, AZ - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Teresa-Struzek/83179e7436a7335a

Detail-oriented, creative and highly motivated Graphic Designer with over

10 years of professional experience working in fast-paced and demanding environments. Solid problem solving, critical thinking and highly organized with the ability to balance time effectively between being a designer, a developer and project leader under strict deadlines.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Graphic Designer/Web Designer**

L'dara/Sorvana - Tempe, AZ - April 2015 to June 2017

- Complete website redesign
- User Interface (UI) design for rebranded Website
- Built and managed multiple WordPress websites
- Email campaign design and HTML development
- Print & Digital Marketing Materials
- Social Media content creation, design and management of all social media platforms
- Product Package Design

### **Graphic Designer**

Walton Internation Group - Scottsdale, AZ - April 2013 to April 2015

Job Responsibilities:

- Housing Development Builder Materials
- Designed brochures, flyers, postcards and PowerPoint decks to support the sales team
- Email campaign design and HTML development
- Maintain and update brand guidelines, ensuring the identity is properly used

## **Graphic Designer/Web Designer**

Mind Streams - Phoenix, AZ - February 2010 to April 2013

Job Responsibilities:

- Complete web and user interface design
- WordPress blog design and website management
- · Email campaign design and HTML development
- Landing page, microsite and form design
- Developed digital and print marketing materials
- Managed team of off-site designers and content writers
- Designed conference materials including invitation brochures,

banners, programs, workbooks and promotional materials

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Bachelor of Arts in Graphic Design**

The Art Institute of Phoenix - Phoenix, AZ 2007

## **Associates of Arts in General Studies**

Scottsdale Community College - Mesa, AZ 2005

LINKS

http://www.struzekdesigns.com